Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
- Landscape Architecture Drawings, / Date(s): ca. 1941 - ca. 1995; 0000; / Quantity: ca. 483 tubes; 128 folders; 2 boxes / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - Hollin Hills / Lot #390, / Date(s): 1955; Folder: 05010; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 77x60cm. / Medium: Pencil; ink stamp / Support: Tracing vellum
  - Hollin Hills /, / Date(s): 1955; Folder: 05011; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 77x60cm. / Medium: Pencil; ink stamp / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Detail drawings for screening/fencing elements. Lot not indicated.
  - Hollin Hills /, / Date(s): 1955; Folder: 05012; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 77x60cm. / Medium: Pencil; ink stamp / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Detail drawings porch elements; lot not indicated.
  - Hollin Hills /, / Date(s): 1955; Folder: 05013; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 77x60cm. / Medium: Pencil; ink stamp / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Various detail drawings for elements of roof, screening panels and porch; lot not indicated.
  - Hollin Hills /, / Date(s): 1954 - 1997; Folder: 05014; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 77x60cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Ancillary material related to Hollin Hills; includes two sets (one reduced) of individual property plans and a mounted site plan of the entire development.
  - Dunn Residence, / Date(s): 1988; Tube: 05015; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: <76x91cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary landscape plan and topo for Charlotte residence of, possibly, Chris and Kathleen (Kiley) Dunn.
  - Equivest Residence, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 05016; / Quantity: 8 / Dimensions: <160x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Architect's drawings, together with preliminary site plan marked "Georgetown Centre Bldg."
    Note: ODK storage label indicates "Palastinian [sic] Builders"; "Dead".
    Scale: Vatries.
  - Silver Lake, / Date(s): n.d.; Tube: 05016a; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 36"x36" / Medium: Blueline print; pencil / Support: Paper
    Note: Annotated site map of lake and recreation area.
  - Silver Lake State Park, / Date(s): n.d.; Tube: 05016b; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 36"x36" / Medium: Blueline print; pencil / Support: Paper
    Note: Drawings related to Silver Lake State Park.
  - Greene Residence, / Date(s): 1990; Tube: 05017; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: 107x76cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Partial set of architect's drawings; no evidence of ODK involvement.
  - Phillip William Fisher Residence, / Date(s): 1988; Tube: 05018; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <107x77cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Architect's drawings, together with topographic survey. No evidence of ODK involvement.
  - Irwin Garden/Miller Townhouse, / Date(s): 1973; Tube: 05020; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <106x87cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Identified as "Irwin Garden" on drawings; apparently "Miller Townhouse" job cited in The Complete Works, p. 213.
    Note: The original design of the Italianate garden of the Irwin house in downtown Columbus has been attributed to Arthur Shurcliff.
  - Magens Bay, / Date(s): 1984; Tube: 05022; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <155x104cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Project is not definitively identified; file includes plans and aerial photographs.
  - McBride Property, / Date(s): 1991; Tube: 05023; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: 92x61cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Bound set of survey plans; third sheet annotated.
  - University of Massachusetts, / Date(s): 1990; Tube: 05024; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 83x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Polyester film
    Note: Ink, pencil and zip-a-tone on polyester film; UMASS campus not indicated.
  - Kenneth Dayton Residence, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 05025; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 63x51cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing paper
    Note: Ink, pencil and felt-tip on trace, mounted oon board.
    Location of associated materials: CF. Folder #579, "Kenneth Dayton Residence."
  - SUNY/Fredonia - Athletic Facilities, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 05026; / Quantity: 16 / Dimensions: 146x82cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Bound set of sitework drawings.
    Published in: Cf. THE COMPLETE WORKS..., pp.209-210.
  - State University of New York at Potsdam--Athletic Facilities-Waterfront, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 05027; / Quantity: 7 / Dimensions: 108x77cm. / Medium: Blueline prints Paper / Support: Paper
    Note: Direct connection to ODK not indicated.
    Location of associated materials: See also #0555 and #0729.
  - Orchid Bay, / Date(s): 1994; Tube: 05028; / Quantity: 17 / Dimensions: <126x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Content: Drawings (several definitiely in the hand of DK) in felt-tip pen and pencil on trace.
  - Bissell Companies, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 05029; / Quantity: 19 / Dimensions: <107x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated plans accompanied by documents and memoranda.
  - Olympic Village and Park, / Date(s): 1983; Tube: 05030; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: <107x76cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Melange of prints and sketches.
  - Portugal Competition, / Date(s): 1984; Tube: 05031; / Quantity: 20 / Dimensions: <24"x48" / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings for an unidentified (luxury apartments? office park?).
    Note: Landscape features and infrastructure include atria, palm and orange trees, pools and parking lots.
  - Cummins Creamery Site, / Date(s): 1976; Tube: 05032; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 67x61cm. / Medium: Ink; zip-a-tone / Support: Polyester film
    Note: One of multiple projects undertaken for the Cummins firm.
  - Saks Center, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 05034; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: 108x77cm. / Medium: Blueline / Support: Paper
    Note: Not included on ODK job list; location speculative.
  - Saitama Arena, / Date(s): 1994; Tube: 05035; / Quantity: 98 / Dimensions: <108x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings accompanied by competition materials.
  - University of Chicago / Women's Residence Hall, / Date(s): 1958; Tube: 05036; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 90x60cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Plan drawn in ink and pencil, with stamps.
  - Spanel Residence, / Date(s): 1976; Tube: 05037; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <107x98cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Project not included in the Complete Works. ...
    Note: Also identified on master list as Schwabel House.
  - Texas Research Park, / Date(s): 1987; Tube: 05038; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <94x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated blueline prints acompanied by aerial photograph.
    Note: Location not determined; possibly San Antonio campus of the University of Texas?
  - Schaefer Property, / Date(s): 1978; Tube: 05039; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 54x46cm. / Medium: Pencil / Support: Paper
    Note: Survey of property abutting Kiley property.
  - Vertue Ariel, / Date(s): n.d.; Tube: 05040; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <132x61cm. / Medium: Xerographic copy / Support: Paper
    Note: Plans for sailboat once owned by Dan Kiley.
  - North Wales [Cummins Engine Company], / Date(s): 1993 - 1995; Tube: 05041; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: 108x95cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans executed over a two-year period for this Cummins site.
  - Willard Basin Ski Development, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 05042; / Quantity: 8 / Dimensions: <147x104cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Sepia prints annotated in colored pencil and pencil.
  - Wing's Point, / Date(s): 1956; Tube: 05043; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: <111x76cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Annotated plans of property once owned by Arctic explorer Sir Wilfred Grenfell; subsequently Kiley residence.
  - Zambrano Residence, / Date(s): n.d.; Tube: 05044; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 175x70cm. / Medium: Blueline print / Support: Paper
    Note: Location and date unknown.
  - State of Vermont Capitol Complex, / Date(s): 1967; Tube: 05045; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: <110x90cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans in mixed media for the Capitol grounds.
  - Addenda / GSD Symposium, / Date(s): 1997; Box: A001; / Quantity: 1 / Medium: Audio/Visual / Support: Videotape
    Note: Audio-visual recording of GSD Symposium related to the exhibition, Dan Kiley, Landscape Architect--The First Two Decades, mounted at the GSD, 1997.
    The film includes the complete presentations by the Symposium participants, recorded November 14, 1997.
    "LP speed."
    Published in: Edited texts of selected presentations were published as: "Daniel Urban Kiley: The Early Gardens", Princeton University Press, 1999.
  - Addenda / Cole House, / Date(s): 1949-1954; Box: A002; / Quantity: 3 / Medium: DVDs / Support: Videotape
    Note: Three dvds detailing current condition of exterior and interior of the Theron Cole house, designed by Kiley in 1950.
    One dvd includes site photographs dating from 1949 and construction photographs.
    Photographs dating from 2007 are the work of Landscape Institute student Faith Michaels.
    "Beauty, Function Combine...", published in "The Worcester Telegram", February 7, 1954 also appears on one disc.
  - Addenda / Eldridge House, / Date(s): 1972; Tube: A003; / Quantity: 22 / Dimensions: <63x48cm. / Medium: Pencil; ink; blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Detailed and heavily annotated plans related to the Eldridge House; set of heating plans prepared by John Couture.
    Plans received from current owner, Tony Corwin, with the aid of architect Stephen Tilly, 2008.
    Location of associated materials: See #0914.
    Prints somewhat discolored and faded.
  - Addenda / Corwin House, / Date(s): 1954-1955; Folder: A004; / Quantity: 18 / Dimensions: <76x55cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Drawings, numbered #2-19 for the Corwin house in Lake Placid.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. File #0368.
    Prints are discolored, yellowed at folds.
  - Addenda / Exhibition Materials, / Date(s): 1920ca.-1997; Folder: A005; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <76x55cm. / Medium: Photographs / Support: Paper
    Note: Photographic reproductions of selected site plans and renderings of Kiley projects included in the 1997 GSD exhibition.
    Also included is a portrait of Kiley (ca. 1920?) included in a montage of class photographs and a copy of the exhibition brochure.
Personal Names Index
Adams, ? (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01001
Adams, Bruce [?] (Architect) / Preliminary drawings 0999
Addison, Stuart (Client) / Planting plans 0319
Adjmi, Morris, 1959- (Architect) / Architect's drawings 01260
Alexander, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01161
Allen, Paul (Client) / Site plans 01190
Arneill, Bruce (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0831
Atherton, John (Client) / Plans (Drawings) 0101
Bacon, Edmund N. (Architect/Client) / Landscaping plans 0028
Baker, Louis (Client) / Landscaping plans 0185
Ball, Douglas (Client) / Landscaping plans 01174
Barnard, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0207, 0278
Barnes, Edward Larrabee, 1915-2004 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01085, 01089, 0540, 0542, 0555, 0610, 0759, 0901
Barnes, Edward Larrabee, 1915-2004 (Architect) / Landscaping planss 01017
Barnes, Edward Larrabee, 1915-2004 (Architect) / Preliminary drawings 0523
Barnes, Edward Larrabee, 1915-2004 (Architect) / Master plans 0614
Barnett, D.L. (Client) / Site plans 0258
Barret, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01154
Beale, ? (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01237
Becker, Harold R., (Surveyor) / Survey plans 0819
Beckhard, Herbert (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01080
Beckhard, Herbert (Associated Architect) / Landscaping plans 0444
Beckman, Frederick (Client) / Landscaping plans 0033
Beeson, Duane (Client) / Site plans 0261
Belluschi, Pietro, 1899-1994 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01227
Berla, Julian, d. 1976 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0031
Berla, Julian, d.1976 (Architect} / Landscaping plans 0018
Bierwaltes, ? (Client) / Preliminary drawings 01277
Bleakney, Walker (Client) / Landscaping plans 0030
Bliss, ? (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0439, 0472, 0473
Bliss, Robert (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0671
Blooston, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0322
Booth, John (Client) / Planting plans 0273
Bostwick, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01145
Breuer, Marcel, 1902- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0444
Breuer, Marcel, 1902- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0812
Breuer, Marcel, 1902-1981 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0476
Breuer, Marcel, 1902-1981 (Architect) / Site plans 0942
Breuer, Marcel, 1902-1981 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0436, 0442
Bridgeman, Elizabeth (Client) / Architectural drawings 0402
Briggs, [?] (Client) / Site plans 05007
Bryan, David (Client) / Landscaping plans 01120
Bucksbaum, Myra? (Client) / Site plans 01046
Buffmire, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0321
Burley, Robert (Architect) / Plans (Drawings) 01014
Button, William H. (Former Owner?) / Architectural drawings 0817
Cannon, [Beekman?] (Client) / Landscaping plans 0842
Christie, [?] (Client) / Site plans 05005
Churchill, Winston S. (Winston Spencer), 1874-1965 / Landscaping plans 0714
Coate, Roland E. (Architect) / Sketches 01283
Cobb, Henry Nichols, 1926- (Architect) / Master plans 01186
Cobb, Henry Nichols, 1926- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01062
Coe, Christopher (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01285
Coffin, David P. (Client) / Site plans 0314
Cohen, Irving J. (Client) / Planting plans 0326
Colburn, Ike (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0504
Collier, Charles (Client) / Landscaping plans 0009
Coon, Milton C. (Client) / Site plans 0262
Corwin, Hamilton (Client) / Architectural drawings 0368
Cotrufo, Joseph (Client) / Architectural drawings 0143
Coyne, John C. (Client) / Site plans 0277
Craig, Charles (Client) / Detail drawings 05012
Cret, Paul, 1876-1945 (Architect) / Working drawings 01033
Criswell, William (Client) / Landscaping plans 01062
Criswell, William T. (Client) / Landscaping plans 01104
Culver, David (Client) / Landscaping plans 01199
Cummings, Jack (Client) / Landscaping plans 0997
Cummings, Robert (Client) / Landscaping plans 0945
Currier, [?], [Client] / Planting plans 0459
Dash, Kevin (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01249
Dash, Kevin (Client/Collaborator) / Sketches 01240
Dash. Kevin (Architect) / Sketches 01240
Daugherty, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0263
Davis, Richard (Client) / Landscaping plans 0434
Dayton, Douglas (Client) / Landscaping plans 0439
Dayton, Kenneth (Client) / Landscaping plans 0438, 05025, 0579
Deitcher, [?] (Client / Sketches 01244
Denham, James [?] (Client) / Landscaping plans 0932
Dinkeloo, John, 1918-1981 (Architect) / Planting plans 0592
Dunn, (Client) / Landscaping plans 05015
Dunn, Chris (Landscape Architect) / Grading plans 01121
Eldridge, [?] (Client0 / Master plans 0914
Elliott, James Barton (Client) / Planting plans 0560
Elliott, Osborne (Client) / Landscaping plans 01127
Ernst, Carl W. (Client) / Site plans 0292
Ernst, M.L. (Client) / Planting plans 0328
Evans, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0337
Ewing, ? (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0500
Falls, Gregory (Client) / Architectural drawings 0414
Farrel, N. (Client) / Master plans 0399
Feldman, Charles (Client) / Site plans 0305
Fermi, Enrico, 1901-1954. / Landscaping plans 0693
Field, Julia (Client) / Landscaping plans 01231
Field, Julia Allen (Client) / Schematic drawings 01039
Fine, Barnet (Client) / Landscaping plans 0172
Fisher, Phillip William (Client) / Architectural drawings 05018
Forbes, Peter (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01154
Forbes, Peter (Architect) / Site plans 01190
Foreman, Clark (Client) / Site plans 0019
Fox, Samuel (Client) / Landscaping plans 01172
Frank, A.F.W. (Client) / Planting plans 0295
Freed, James, Ingo (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0597
Freeman, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0281
Gates, Bill (Client) / Landscaping plans 01236
Geffen, David, 1943- (Client) / Sketches 01283
Gile, Richard S. (Client) / Landscaping plans 0191
Girard, Alexander (Designer) / Landscaping plans 0396
Giurgola, Romualdo, 1920- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0438
Goding, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0307
Goodhue, [?] (client) / Site plans 0269
Goodman, Charles M., 1906-1992 (Developer) / Site plans 0332
Granbery, Carleton (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0537
Granbery, Carleton (Architect) / Site plans 0837
Graves, Michael, 1934- (Architect) / Land surveys 0716
Greene, ? (Client) / Working drawings 05017
Gregory, Bill (Client) / Landscaping plans 0504
Gregory, Stanley (Client) / Landscaping plans 0504
Gregory, William (Client) / Landscaping plans 01061
Grenfell, Pascoe (Client) / Architectural drawings 0367
Grenfell, Sir Wilfred Thomason, 1865-1940--Homes & haunts / Survey plans 05043
Griswold, ? (Client) / Site plans 0837
Haffner, Joseph (Architect) / Grading plans 01121
Hall, Donald Joyce (Client) / Landscaping plans 01157
Hall, Joyce C., 1891-1982 (Client) / Master plans 01186
Hamilton, C.O. (Client) / Landscaping plans 01027
Hamilton, Clarence (Client) / Landscaping plans 0573
Hamilton, David (Client) / Landscaping plans 0105
Hamilton (Client) / Landscaping plans 0155
Harrison, Wallace (Wallace Kirkman), 1895- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0883, 0931
Harrison, Wallace K. (Wallace Kirkman), 1895- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0529
Harrison, Wallace K (Wallace Kirkman), 1895- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0613
Hauben, Ben (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01281
Heath, Andy (Client) / Grading plans 01121
Helzberg, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01196
Henderson, S.L. (Client) / Site plans 0308
Henry, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0323
Hetzel, Ralph (Client) / Landscaping plans 0015
Hill, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0291
Hill, D.P. (Client) / Site plans 0299
Hillberry, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01162
Hisaka, Don (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01077
Hisaka, Don (Architect) / Master plans 01007
Hitchcock, L.D. (Client) / Planting plans 0251
Hodgson, Isaac, 1826-? (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0906
Hollander, Edward (Client) / Architectural drawings 0043
Hollander, Edward (Client) / Landscaping plans 0018
Hooper, Mrs. Arthur (Client) / Landscaping plans 0442
Horecki, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0316
Howe, George, 1886-1955 (Architect) / Site plans 0042
Howe, George, 1886-1955 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0015
Hubben, Herbert (Client) / Site plans 0315
Hunter, James (Client) / Landscaping plans 01163
Hunter, Richard A. (Client) / Landscaping plans 0202
Jackling, Daniel, 1869-1956 (Original Owner) / Landscaping plans 01126
Jacobsen, Hugh Newell,1929- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01183
Jacobsen, Hugh Newell, 1929- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01109, 01110, 01172
Jacobsen, Hugh Newell ,1929- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01120
Janeway, Edward (Client) / Planting plans 0606
Janney, Jervis (Client) / Landscaping plans 0977
Jay, William, c.1793-1837 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01028
Jennings, Peter (Client) / Landscape plans 0989
Jobs, Steven, 1955- (Client) / Landscaping plans 01126
Johnson, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0268
Johnson, Jed (Designer) / Landscaping plans 01172
Johnson, Philip, 1906-2005 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0434
Johnson, Philip, 1906-2005 (Architect) / Planting plans 0478
Johnson, Ted (Client)? / Landscaping plans 0671
Jones, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0300
Jones, Mrs. Carl (Client) / Landscaping plans 0472
Jones, Rees L. (Designer) / Site plans 0593
Jones, Robert Trent (Designer) / Site plans 0593
Kahn, Louis I., 1901-1974 (Architect) / Site plans 0042
Kaitz, Hyman (Client) / Planting plans 0259
Kanarek, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0336
Kandrian, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01162
Kassler, Kenneth (Architect/Owner) / Landscaping plans 0190
Kassler, Kenneth (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0030, 0033
Kastner, Alfred (Architect) / Site plans 0019
Kaufman, Stanley (Client) / Architectural drawings 0232
Kenen, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0257
Kennedy, Robert Woods (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0205, 0363
Ketchum, Morris, jr. (Architect) / Survey plans 0819
Keyes, [?] (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0511
Keyes, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0297
Kiley, Dan (Architect) / Plans (Drawings) 0101
Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004 / Landscaping plans (Collection), 0000
Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban) (Owner) / Architectural drawings 05040
Kiley, Dan -- Homes & haunts / Survey plans 05043
Kleinfeld, Irving (Client) / Planting plans 0296
Klenk, H.S. (Client) / Site plans 0264
Knowles, James (Client) / Architectural drawings 0836
Koch, Carl, 1907-1993 (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01163, 0202
Krieger, Seymour (Client) / Landscaping plans 0436
Kuhn, Howard R. (Client) / Site plans 0282
Kusko, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01311
Laaff, George (Client) / Landscaping plans 0444
Lane, J.R. (Client) / Site plans 0294
Lasker, Albert D., 1880-1952 / Planting plans 0385
Lasker, Mary (Client) / Planting plans 0385
Lear, Norman (Client) / Landscaping plans 01237, 01239
Leighton, R.M. (Client) / Site plans 0301
Lewis, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01128
Lewis, [Charles ? ](Client) / Landscaping plans 01129
Lewis-Hobart, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01144
Lillich, James and Sherrie (Clients) / Landscaping plans 01285
London, John (Client) / Planting plans 0265
Lorimer, C.H. (Client) / Planting plans 0285
Lyles, ? (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0492
Macaluso, Vincent (Client) / Site plans 0256
Macklowe, Harry (Client) / Landscaping plans 01271
Macomber, Blair (Client) / Architectural drawings 0145
Martin, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0340
Maurer, Stanley (Project Architect) / Landscaping plans 0540
Maynard, ? (Client) / Landscaping plans 01040
McBride, ? (Client) / Survey plans 05023
Medvin, Norman (Client) / Site plans 0254
Meier, Richard (Architect) / Preliminary drawings 01258
Melbourn, P.A. (Client) / Landscaping plans 01249
Mellon, Rachel Lambert (Mrs. Paul) / Sketches 01003
Metz, Don (Renovation Architect) / Landscaping plans 0918
Michela, [?] (Client) / Site plans 05008
Miller, [?] (Client) / Site plans 05009
Miller, Doug (Client) / Plans (Drawings) 01006
Miller, Irwin, 1909-2004 (Client) / Landscaping plans 0396
Miller, Irwin [?] / Landscaping plans 05020
Miller, J. Irwin (Client) / Landscaping plans 0607, 0608
Miner, R.M. (Client) / Site plans 0330
Mitchell, Rod (Client) / Landscaping plans 01251
Mogin, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0325
Molner, John (Restoration Architect) / Landscaping plans 01028
Moore, Henry, 1898- / Landscaping plans 01159
Moore, Henry, 1898-1986 (Sculptor) / Landscaping plans 0693
Moore, R. Scott (Client) / Site plans 0276
Mosher, Gregory (Client) / Landscaping plans 01194
Moyer, Mrs. Herbert (Client) / Landscaping plans 0023
Mumma, A.C. (Client) / Site plans 0293
Netsch, Walter A., jr. (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0693
Newfield, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0339
Newlin, George (Client) / Landscaping plans 0575
Newsham, [?] (Client) / Site plans 0306
Niles, Louville F. (Client) / Landscaping plans 0512
Odoroff, [?] (Client) / Planting plans 0304
Odum, Raymond (Client) / Planting plans 0279
Olmsted, Frederick Law, 1822-1903 (Landscape Architect) / Master plans 0951
Ostrowski, W.L. (Client) / Site plans 0312
Pearson, Dr. Robert (Client) / Architectural drawings 0366
Pei, I.,M., 1917- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0597
Pei, I.M., 1917- (Architect) / Competition drawings 01223
Pei, I.M., 1917- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01221
Pei, I.M., 1917- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01155, 0825
Pei, I.M., 1917- (Architect) / Site plans 0909
Pei, I.M., 1917- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01153
Pei, I.M. ,1917- (Architect) / Landscaping plans 01062
Pei, I.M., 1917- (Architect) / Sketches 01003
Pfeifle, ? (Architect) / Landscaping plans 0481
Phelan, Ellen (Client) / Landscaping plans 01133
Phillips, George W. (Client) / Site plans 0252
Pillsbury, George (Client) / Landscaping plans 0473